Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.thirt Mss.B.B61.inventory13
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents T
  - Thesun (Box 88)
    - See Gruepe, 1909 Apr. 14
  - Thilenius, G. Dr. (Box 88)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 3p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 17
    - See Luschan, F. von, 1913 Aug. 3
  - Thilly, Frank (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p
  - Thode, Henry (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 12; 1p
  - Thomas (Box 89)
    - From Vincent, G.E., 1908 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1907 May 14
  - Thomas, Miss (Box 89)
    - Found at end of Mar. 1942, 2p
  - Thomas, Miss A. E. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1917 May 23
    - To Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 May 21
  - Thomas, Calvin Prof. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 20; 9p
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 May 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 2
  - Thomas, Charles C. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Thomas, Prof. Cyrus (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 10
  - Thomson, David (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 17; 1p
  - Thomas, D. L. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 10
  - Thomas, Miss Dorothy Swaine (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 7; 1p
  - Thomas, Elmer (Box 89)
    - To "to whom it may concern", 1937 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Thomas, F. W. (Box 89)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Jan. 11
  - Thomas, George (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 12; 2p
  - Thomas, H. P. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 4
  - Thomas, N. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 3; 1p
  - Thomas, Northcote W. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1907 July 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 July 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 11
  - Thomas, Paul B. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 27; 1p
  - Thomas, Wendell M -- to Boas, 1913 May 20 (Box 89)
  - Thomas, Wilbur K. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 2
    - Enc. Schmidt-Ott Memorandum, 1930 Oct. 15; 3p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 19; 1p
    - Found at end of 1930, 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 6; 1p
    - To Hepburn, A. Barton, 1920 Jan. 31; 1p
    - To Heuser, F.W.J., 1932 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Kandel, I.L., 1934 Sep. 24
    - Enc. with Kandel, I.L., 1935 Jan. 22
    - To Mason, J.A., 1940 Nov. 7; 1p
    - Enc. with Wilbur, W.K., 1940 Nov. 12
    - From Mason, J.A., 1940 Nov. 5
    - Enc. with Wilbur, W.K., 1940 Nov. 12
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1930 Nov. 14
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1930 Dec. 17
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1931 Feb. 5; 3p
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1931 Mar. 30; 3p
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1931 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Members of the Carl Schurz Memorial Foundation, 1931 May 11; 3p
  - Thomas, William I. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1907 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1910 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 14
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 21
  - Thomas, W. M. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1913 May 20
  - Thompson, A. H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 3; 2p
  - Thompson, Anna (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 19; 1p
  - Thompson, C. H. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1928 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 23; 1p
  - Thompson, Dorothy (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 19; 1p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Black, W.), 1939 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas Found at end of Dec. 1939, 3p
  - Thompson, E. H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 6; 2p
  - Thompson, F. K. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 23
  - Thompson, J. A. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Thompson, John B. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 20; 1p
  - Thompson, Lincoln (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 July 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 1; 1p
  - Thompson, N. S. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1932 May 9; 1p
    - To Butler, N.M., 1933 Mar. 17; 1p
    - Enc. with Hayden, P.M., 1933 Mar. 21
    - To Butler, N.M., 1934 Apr. 25; 1p
    - From Fackenthal, F.D., 1934 Apr. 27
    - To Hayden, P. M., 1935 Jan. 11; 1p
  - Thompson, Randall (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 4
  - Thompson, Stith (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 May 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 3; 1p
  - Thompson, T. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1927 July 16; 1p
  - Thompson, T. C. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 8
  - Thompson, Thomas H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Thompson & Fuller (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
  - Thompson Tales Index (Box 89)
    General note
    Not located 6/8/79
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec.
  - Thomson, D. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1928 June 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 12; 1p
    - Enc. his letters to Adamson, T., 1927 Oct. 11
    - And Jacobs, M., 1927 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1928 June 13; 1p
    - To Adamson, T., 1927 Oct. 11; 1p
    - Enc. with Thomson, D., 1927 Oct. 12
    - To Jacobs, M., 1927 Oct. 11
    - Enc. with Thomson, D., 1927 Oct. 12
  - Thone, Frank (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 8; 1p
  - Thoothi, N. A. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 18; 1p
  - Thorburn, G. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 1
  - Thorert, W. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Thorndike (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 18
    - See Boas, F. (to Giddings, F.H.), 1913 Jan. 18
  - Thorndike, Ashley Horace (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 12; 4p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p
    - To Butler, N.M., 1919 Oct. 30
    - Enc. Plan for Faculty of Philosophy., 7p
  - Thorndike, Edward L. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 25; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Woodworth, R.S.), 1931 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 17; 1p
  - Thorndike, Lynn (Box 89)
    - See Wiener, Philip Paul, 1938 Nov. 30
  - Thornelili, E. C. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
  - Thost (Box 89)
    - To Correns, 1924 July 23; 1p
  - Thrason, O. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 13
  - Thristirn, Willem (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 7; 2p
  - Throop, A. M. (Box 89)
    - To Sapir, E., 1918 Aug. 15; 1p
  - Thun, Ferdinand (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 30; 1p
    - From Schmidt-Ott
    - See enc. Schmidt-Ott, 1931 Oct. 3
  - Thurlow, P. E. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 21; 1p
  - Thurnwald, Dr. Richard (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Branham, L.G., 1936 Feb. 25
    - To Branham, L.G., 1936 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Lewy, 1936 Oct. 26
  - Thwing, Charles F. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 25; 2p
  - Thyler, R. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Tibbetts, M. P. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Barnes, H.E., 1918 July 8
  - Tiemann & Co., George (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 26
  - Tilderby, M. H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 26; 8p
  - Tildesley, Miss M. L. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 30; 2p
  - Tilghman, Z. A. (Box 89)
    - See Key, W.S., 1936 Mar. 2
  - Tillich, Paul (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 29; 2p
  - Tilney, Frederick (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 2; 1p
  - Timbres, R. J. (Box 89)
    - See Brewstern, Dorothy, 1939 July 18
  - Time, Editor of letters (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 8; 4p
      See also Potter, J C
  - Time, Leo (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 12; 3p
  - Times (London) (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18
  - Tinkham, G. H. (Box 89)
    - From Lansing, R., 1917 Mar. 9
  - Tinney, M. C. (Box 89)
    - To Bertheau, R. C., 1938 Feb. 18; 1p
    - Enc. with Osborn, F., 1938 Mar. 11
  - Titchener, E. B. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 19
  - Tittle, E. F. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 4
  - Tiürczny (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 14; 5p
  - Tjebbes, Ruth (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 30; 1p
  - Today (Box 89)
    - See Moley, Raymond-, 3-31-36, 4-1-36
    - See Yates, Haydie, 4-2-36, 5-29-36
  - Todd, Albert M. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1925 May 16; 1p
  - Todd, Arthur J. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Todd, B. A. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 7
  - Todd, C. C. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 25; 2p
  - Todd, Fred N. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 1; 1p
  - Todd, H. A. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 27
  - Todd, M. S. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 2; 1p
  - Todd, T. Wingate (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 May 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct.; 1p 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p
    - Enc. Ashley-Montagu, M.F., 1931 Apr. 2
    - Ashley-Montagu, M.F. -- Bibliography of papers, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 4; 1p
    - Enc. Todd, T.W. Instrumentation for studies in the determination of population qualities., 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 June 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Hooten, E. A., 1935 Nov. 2; 2p
  - Toel (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 6
  - Toennies, Ferdinand (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Apr.; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 9
    - To Boas, 1882 Aug. 6
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 21; 1p
  - Toennies, Dr. Gerrit (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 17 end Dec; 1p
  - Toennies, L. F., 1936 April. 21; 1p. (Box 89)
  - Toldt, Karl (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 18; 1p
  - Toledo, Archbishop (Box 89)
    - From Goma, I. Cardinal, 1937 June 7
  - Toller, Ernst (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 10; 1p
  - Tolman, A. H. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Tolstoi über den Antisemitismus (Box 89)
    See Teneromo, I.
    - Found at end of Dec. 1911
  - Tombo, Rudolph, Jr. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 July 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Tomeny, A. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Tomkins, W. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 1; 2p
  - Tomlinson, P. G. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Tompkins, A. F. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 3
  - Ton (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1899 Nov. 16
  - Tong, Jocelyn (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 May 18; 1p
  - Toni (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 15; 4p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 8; 4p
  - Tonjes, D. H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 15
  - Tooker, W. W. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1899 Feb. 7
  - Toomey, N. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Toor, Frances (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 21; 1p
      See Boas, F. (to Moe, H.A.)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1931
  - Topeka, Librarian of the State Library (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 16; 4p
  - Topinard, P. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 4
  - Torday, E. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
  - Torres, Heloise Alberto (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1941 May 6; 1p
  - Torres, J. M. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1915 July 15
  - Torres, L. M. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p
  - Torrey, Norman L. (Box 89)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Tory, H. M. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 3; 1p
  - Toth, Rudolph S. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1920 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 11; 3p
  - Totten, I. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Toussaint, C. M. (Box 89)
    - From Castillo LedC3n, L., 1922 July 24; 2p
  - Tout, Charles Hill (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 2
  - Tow (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 3
  - Tower, R. S. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 24
  - Tower, Ralph W. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1920 July 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 21
    - From Brill, E.J., 1920 Aug. 13; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Lucas, F. A., 1920 Oct. 4
    - From Brill, E. J., 1920 Aug. 13; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Lucas, F. A., 1920 Oct. 4; 1p
    - From Brill, E. J., 1920 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Brill, E. J., 1921 Mar. 7; 2p
    - From Brill, E. J., 1921 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Brill, E. J., 1924 Oct. 31; 1p
  - Towne, A. W. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1918 July 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 9; 1p
  - Towne, Helen L. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 16; 1p
  - Townsend, C. H. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1910 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 31; 1p
      Note: see carbon copy
  - Townsend, E. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Townsend, W. C. (Box 89)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 29; 1p
    - See Townsend, C. H., 1928 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Sapir, E., 1937 May 27; 1p
    - To Swadesh, M., 1937 May 25; 2p
  - Tows (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1899 May 1
  - Toy, C. H. (Box 89)
    - To Boas, 1891 Mar. 18
  - Tozzer, Alfred M. (Box 90-91)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 26; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1908 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1908 May 4
    - From Boas, 1908 May 11
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
    - From Boas, 1908 June 24
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 20